In this section, we're going to explore the
En esta seccin, vamos a explorar los fundamentos
fundamentals of unit testing. So you're going to learn about characteristics
de las pruebas unitarias. Entonces aprenders sobre las caractersticas
of good unit tests. What to test and what not to test,
de las buenas pruebas unitarias. Qu probar y qu no evaluar, esta
this is one of the common questions I get from a lot of my students,
es una de las preguntas ms frecuentes que recibo de muchos de mis alumnos.
they say, "Mosh, I don't know what to test!" So in this section, I'm going to give you some
Dicen: "Mosh, no s qu probar! "Entonces en esta seccin, voy a darle
guidelines that help you get started. You're also going to learn about
algunas pautas que lo ayudarn a comenzar. Tambin aprender a nombrar y
naming and organizing your tests, along with some basic
organizar sus pruebas, junto con algunas tcnicas bsicas para escribir
techniques for writing clean and maintainable tests. And finally you're
pruebas limpias y mantenibles. Y finalmente aprenders
going to learn how to write reliable tests that don't lie.
cmo escribir pruebas confiables que no mientan.
So, when they pass, you know that your production code is working,
Entonces, cuando pasan, sabes que tu cdigo de produccin est funcionando, y
and when they fail, you know that there is something wrong in the production code.
cuando fallan, sabes que hay algo mal en el cdigo de produccin.
So now, let's get started!
As que ahora, empecemos!